{
    "subject": "Elena_of_Montenegro",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Victor_Emmanuel_III_of_Italy",
    "human_readable": "Elena of Montenegro is married to Victor Emmanuel III of Italy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9777911305427551,
            "question": "What is Elena of Montenegro's relationship to Victor Emmanuel III of Italy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9314815402030945,
            "question": "Who is Victor Emmanuel III of Italy married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9070526361465454,
            "question": "To whom was Elena of Montenegro married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6179949641227722,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Elena of Montenegro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6055216193199158,
            "question": "Was Elena of Montenegro related to any Italian monarchs?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5742905735969543,
            "question": "Who was the queen consort of Italy during the reign of Victor Emmanuel III?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4471817910671234,
            "question": "What role did Elena of Montenegro play in Italian society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4218564033508301,
            "question": "Can you name any significant events that occurred during the reign of Victor Emmanuel III?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3289438784122467,
            "question": "Was Victor Emmanuel III a popular monarch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10072683542966843,
            "question": "Who was the king of Italy during the early 20th century?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Elena of Montenegro is married to Victor Emmanuel III of Italy.",
            "html": "yago_25515_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Victor Emmanuel III a popular monarch?",
            "html": "yago_25515_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any significant events that occurred during the reign of Victor Emmanuel III?",
            "html": "yago_25515_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role did Elena of Montenegro play in Italian society?",
            "html": "yago_25515_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_25515_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide clear information that Princess Elena of Montenegro was married to Victor Emmanuel III, who was the King of Italy. This supports the statement that Elena of Montenegro is married to Victor Emmanuel III of Italy."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}